onlinesales.ai 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy | OnlineSales.ai

At OnlineSales.ai, we respect the privacy rights of our users and recognize the importance of protecting the personal information we collect about you. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand what information we collect and how we use and share that information. This Privacy Policy applies to our Websites and Services.

As used in this Privacy Policy, **“OnlineSales.ai,”** **“us”** and **“we”** refers to OnlineSales, Inc. The **“Websites”** means OnlineSales.ai’s websites (including without limitation https://onlinesales.ai, https://apps.onlinesales.ai, https://audit.onlinesales.ai, https://knowledge.onlinesales.ai, https://c.o-s.io and any successor URLS, mobile or localized versions and related domains and subdomains), and the **“Services”** means OnlineSales.ai’s products, applications and services, in each case in whatever format they may be offered now or in the future. The Websites and Services are collectively referred to herein as the **“Offerings.”**

This Privacy Notice explains how, why, and when we collect data from you on our Offerings. Your continued use of our offerings following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## About OnlineSales.ai’s Services

OnlineSales.ai provides various services, including but not limited to, digital media marketing, data analytics, social media and advertising management, campaign management & optimization, etc. for our clients (“Advertisers”). 

## What Information this Privacy Policy Covers

This Privacy Policy covers information we collect from you through our Site. Some of our Site’s functionality can be used without revealing any Personally Identifiable Information, though for features or services related to the OnlineSales.ai, Personally Identifiable Information is required. In order to access certain features and benefits on our Site, you may need to submit, or we may collect, “Personally Identifiable Information” (i.e., information that can be used to identify you). Personally Identifiable Information can include information such as your name and email address, among other things. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to OnlineSales.ai. Inaccurate information may affect your ability to use the Site, the information you receive when using the Site, and our ability to contact you. For example, your email address should be kept current because that is one of the primary manners in which we communicate with you.

## What You Agree to by Using Our Site

Please understand that by submitting any Personally Identifiable Information to us, you consent and agree that we may collect, use and disclose such Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and as permitted or required by law. If you do not agree with these terms, please do not provide any Personally Identifiable Information to us. If you refuse or withdraw your consent, or if you choose not to provide us with any required Personally Identifiable Information, we may not be able to provide you with the services that can be offered on our Site. Please note that we may also rely on legitimate interests or fulfillment of a contract to continue processing your data.

## What Data We Collect and How We Use It

We may collect the following categories of information on our website and use them for the purposes explained below.

  1. **Website activity:** Data about your browsing activity on our website.
  2. **Device and browser information:** Technical information about the device or browser you use to access our website.
  3. **Registration and Contact Information:** We collect information about you when you register to use the Services and otherwise provide contact information via email, mail, Linkedin Oauth or through our Websites. This information you provide may include your name, email address, mailing address or phone number.
  4. **Customer Service Information:** Information you may provide to customer service including survey responses.
  5. **Payment Information:** When you purchase the Services, we also collect transaction information, which may include your credit card type, billing and mailing address, and other payment-related information Please note that this information is collected directly by our payments processor and not stored at OnlineSales.ai.
  6. **Third party information:** We may collect information when you interact with our advertisements and other content on third-party sites or platforms, such as social networking sites. This may include information such as “Likes”, profile information gathered from social networking sites or the fact that you viewed or interacted with content served by us or our Advertisers.
  7. **Use of Intercom Services:** We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom’s use of cookies, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.
  8. **Other Information:** We may collect other information from you that is not specifically listed here. We may use any such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy or as otherwise permitted by you.

## We Use This Data To

  * To provide, maintain and improve the Offerings and our other products and services, including to operate certain features and functionality of the Offerings (for example, by remembering your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during this or subsequent visits)
  * To process your inquiries and otherwise deliver customer service.
  * To process your payments, we share and use Payment Information as described in Payment Information section.
  * To control unauthorized use or abuse of the Offerings and our other products and services, or otherwise detect, investigate or prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal.
  * To analyze trends, administer or optimize the Offerings, monitor usage or traffic patterns (including to track users’ movements around the Offerings) and gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
  * To communicate directly with you, including by sending you newsletters, promotions and special offers or information about new products and services. Your opt-out options for promotional communications are described in the Your Choices and Opting Out section.
  * To deliver you advertising, including by serving and managing ads on the Offerings or on third party sites and to tailor ads based on your interests and browsing history.
  * Please see ‘Your Choices and Opting Out section’, for additional information on how to manage the ads you see; and in the manner described to you at the time of collection or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

## Data Sharing

We may disclose personally identifying information (PII) about you:

  1. With our service providers: Companies we contract with who help with parts of our business operations. We require that our service providers only use your PII in connection with the services they perform for us.
  2. With your service providers: Companies under contract with, or acting on your behalf, who handle data (such as a customer lists) on your behalf.
  3. With our subsidiaries and related companies.
  4. In connection with legal proceedings: When we are under a legal obligation to do so, for example, to comply with a binding order of a court, or where disclosure is necessary to exercise, establish or defend the legal rights of OnlineSales.ai, our Advertisers or any other third party.
  5. In connection with a sale of our business: If a third party acquires some or all of our business or assets, we may disclose your PII in connection with the sale.

We also share technical data that we collect about your browsing habits and your device (such as data relating to our cookies, tracking pixels and similar technologies) with other advertising companies in the digital advertising ecosystem. This enables them and us to serve you better and provide quality services.

Finally, we may disclose aggregated, anonymized information to our Advertisers and other third parties.

## Cookies and Related Technologies

Our Offerings uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies that assist us in providing you a better, more personalized experience. Cookies are small data files that are served by our Offerings or other third parties and stored on your device. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the website to target ads to you on other websites.

User may choose to set their [web browser to refuse cookies](https://onlinesales.ai/cookie-policy/), or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of our Websites may not function properly.

### Your Choices and Opting-Out

We recognize how important your online privacy is to you, so we offer the following options for controlling the targeted ads you receive and how we use your data:

**Opt-Outs:** You can [opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us. ](https://onlinesales.ai/cookie-policy/)Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt-out on each browser or device. If you opt-out, we may collect some data about your online activity for operational purposes (such as fraud prevention) but it won’t be used by us for the purpose of targeting ads to you. If you decide to opt-out, we may not be able to provide certain features of our Offerings to you.

**Communication Preferences.** If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included on such communications or on the Offerings. Please note, however, that you may be unable to opt-out of certain service-related communications.

**Blocking Cookies.** You can remove or block certain cookies using the settings in your browser but the Offerings may cease to function properly if you do so. For more information, please see OnlineSales.ai’s Cookie Policy.

**How We Respond to Do Not Track Signals.** You can opt-out of our tracking your online activity for targeted advertising purposes (Do Not Track): We respond to “do not track” or “DNT” signals sent from your browser. If the website of one of our Advertisers receives a DNT signal, during that visit, we will not link data we collect to your browser identifier so that new data collected about you will not be used by us for targeted advertising purposes, but older data collected about you may still be used.

## Payment Information

When you make a purchase on the Offerings, any credit card information you provide as part of your Payment Information is collected and processed directly by our payment processor Stripe through their Stripe Checkout service. We never receive or store your full credit card information. Stripe commits to complying with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) and using industry standard security. Stripe may use your Payment Information in accordance with their own Privacy Policy here: https://stripe.com/us/checkout/legal.

## Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

When you use the Offerings, we make sincere efforts to provide you with access to your personal information upon your request and either provide you the means to correct this information if it is inaccurate or to delete such information at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. You may access, review, correct, update, change or delete your information at any time. To do so, please contact us at [privacy@onlinesales.ai](mailto:privacy@onlinesales.ai) with your name and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed. We may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), jeopardize the privacy of others, would be extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

Please note that if you cease using the Service or we terminate your access to the Service in accordance with your Customer Agreement, you may no longer have the ability to access or update your information.

We may retain your information as necessary to support the Offerings, comply with our legal obligations or resolve disputes. Note that content you post may remain on the Offerings even if you cease using the Offerings or we terminate your access to the Offerings.

## Information About Children

The Offerings are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13, nor does OnlineSales.ai knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, you may not attempt to register for the Offerings or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. In the event that we confirm that we have collected personal information from someone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information promptly. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 and believe that we might have any information from or about such child, please contact us at the email or mailing address provided at the end of this Privacy Policy.

## Data Retention

PII is held no longer than necessary for our business purposes or to meet legal requirements.

## Security

We apply technical, administrative and organizational security measures to protect the data we collect against accidental or unlawful destruction and loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network, and against other unlawful forms of processing.

## International Transfers

We may transfer the information we collect about you to countries other than the country where we originally collected it for the purposes of storage and processing of data and operating our services. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as your country. However, when we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Notice.

## Third party Websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Websites that link to the website and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these website and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Websites. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Websites, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this page. If we make a material change to our privacy practices, we will provide notice on the site or by other means as appropriate.

## Contact us about questions or concerns

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our privacy practices, or GDPR, you can contact [legal-finance@onlinesales.ai](mailto:legal-finance@onlinesales.ai) .

**Attn:** Legal Department, No. 35, Deep Complex, 1st Floor, Above Renault Showroom, Mumbai – Bangalore Highway, Baner, Pune – 411045. Phone: 091-20-6625-0000
